Welcome back, and let's take a look at the correct code statements
مرحبًا بعودتك، دعنا نلقِ نظرة على جمل الكود الصحيحة
needed to implement each of these comments.
المطلوبة لتنفيذ كل هذه التعليقات.
So for this first comment here, asking us to create a new ArrayList object
بالنسبة للتعليق الأول هنا، الذي يطلب منا إنشاء عنصر ArrayList جديد
called restaurantsToTry, and containing a list of strings.
يُدعى restaurantsToTry، ويحتوي على قائمة سلاسل.
The code for that looks like this.
يبدو ذلك الكود هكذا.
So we have ArrayList of type String,
إذن لدينا ArrayList من نوع سلسلة،
the object name restaurantsToTry = new ArrayList of type String.
اسم العنصر هو  restaurantsToTry يساوي ArrayList جديدة من نوع String.
And note that when instantiating an ArrayList,
ولاحظ أنه عند إنشاء مثيل ArrayList،
we don't need to input any parameters here.
لا نحتاج لإدخال أية معلمات هنا.
Now for this second comment, asking us to add a restaurant called
والآن بالنسبة للتعليق الثاني، الذي يطلب منا إضافة مطعم يُدعى
Morning Cafe to the ArrayList, the code looks like this.
Morning Cafe إلى ArrayList، يبدو الكود هكذا.
So we have restaurantsToTry.add and it's taking in Morning Cafe as its input.
إذن لدينا restaurantsToTry.add ويأخذ Morning Cafe كإدخاله.
So here's what that looks like visually.
إليك كيف يبدو ذلك بصورة مرئية.
So using our .add method,
إذن باستخدام أسلوب .add،
we've added Morning Cafe at the zeroth index of our restaurantsToTry ArrayList.
أضفنا Morning Cafe عند المؤشر الصفري لـrestaurantsToTry ArrayList.
So now onto the third comment,
وننتقل الآن إلى التعليق الثالث،
asking us to add another restaurant called BBQ Time.
الذي يطلب منا إضافة مطعم آخر يُدعى BBQ Time.
So the code looks really similar.
يبدو الكود متشابهًا حقًا.
We have restaurantsToTry.add, and
لدينا restaurantsToTry.add،
this time, it's taking in BBQ Time as its input parameter.
وهذه المرة، إنه يأخذ BBQ Time كمعلمته للإدخال.
So here's the code again, and this time,
وها هنا الكود مجددًا، وهذه المرة،
we're adding in BBQ Time as the first index of this ArrayList.
نُضيف BBQ Time كأول مؤشر في ArrayList.
So now onto our fourth comment.
وننتقل الآن إلى التعليق الرابع،
So the user has just tried our Morning Cafe restaurant.
إذن المستخدم جرب مطعم Morning Cafe فحسب،
So we want to go ahead and remove it from our ArrayList.
وبالتالي نريد المضي قدمًا وإزالته من ArrayList.
So all we need to do is use the restaurantsToTry.remove method, and
لذلك كل ما نحتاج لفعله هو استخدام أسلوب restaurantsToTry.remove،
then take in Morning Cafe as its parameter.
ومن ثم أخذ Morning Cafe كمعلمته.
So for our fourth comment, the user has just tried our Morning Cafe restaurant,
وبالنسبة للتعليق الرابع، جرّب المستخدم مطعم Morning Cafe فقط،
and so we just want to remove it from the restaurant's ArrayList now.
ولذلك نريد إزالته فقط من ArrayList الخاصة بالمطعم الآن.
So the code for that looks like this, restaurantsToTry.remove, and
ويبدو الكود لذلك هكذا، restaurantsToTry.remove،
it takes in Morning Cafe as its input parameter.
ويأخذ Morning Cafe كمعلمته للإدخال.
So visually, using the .remove method, we remove Morning Cafe and that shrinks
إذن بصورة مرئية، باستخدام أسلوب .remove، نُزيل Morning Cafe وهذا يُقلّص
the size of the array and moves BBQ Time up to the zeroth index of the ArrayList.
حجم المصفوفة ويُحرّك BBQ Time للأعلى إلى المؤشر الصفري للـArrayList.
So onto our last comment.
وننتقل إلى التعليق الأخير،
So we want to get the length of the list and
نريد الحصول على طول القائمة
then store it in an integer called numberOfRestaurants.
ومن ثم تخزينه بعدد طبيعي يُدعى numberOfRestaurants.
So the code for that looks like this.
إذن يبدو الكود لذلك هكذا.
We have int numberOfRestaurants = restaurantsToTry.size.
لدينا  numberOfRestaurants = restaurantsToTry.size.
Remember for ArrayList, when we use the method size, it doesn't take in any
تذكّر أنه بالنسبة لـArrayList، عندما نستخدم حجم الأسلوب، لا يأخذ أية
input parameters and it retrieves for us the number of elements in the list.
معلمات إدخال ويسترجع لنا عدد العناصر في القائمة.
So in our case right now, the size of the ArrayList is just one.
لذلك في حالتنا هذه الآن، يكون حجم ArrayList هو واحد فقط.
[BLANK_AUDIO].
[BLANK_AUDIO]